# Raul Mateo Beneyto

#### Software Engineer

I am a self-driven person who enjoys learning and creating all kinds of projects. Not only I relish working as a team as it requires communication and dedication, but also I have an open mind to new ideas and appreciate learning from others with more knowledge and experience. In addition, I am a positive person who enjoys maintaining the enthusiasm in a work environment.



raulmateob@gmail.com

Barcelona, Spain

in Raul Mateo Beneyto

+34 691014930

raulmabe.dev

/raulmabe

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Full-stack Developer at iThinkUPC

As part of a multi-disciplinary web development team, I was responsible for the development and maintenance of a multi-user web application.

- MVC Architecture
- Java, SpringBoot, Lombok, Hibernate
- Scrum and Kanban Board with Jira

Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020

### Front-end Developer at Jumpets

As a member of a start-up, I developed a website and a multiplatform application.

- MVC Architecture
- Flutter, BLoC and Redux patterns
- PHP, Laravel and Blade

Jun. 2019 - Sep. 2020

# **EDUCATION**

### Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering majored in Software Engineering

Final thesis grade 92%

Sep. 2015 - Dec. 2020

### Personal Projects at raulmabe.dev

Love trying new technologies, tools, patterns and techniques. I encourage you to check some of my projects in my website, where I some mock-ups along with explanation about each one.

always

### **PROGRAMMING**

**★** Flutter

**★** Dart

**★** ReactJS

**★** Typescript **★** Vuejs GatsbyJS

SASS

CSS

 SpringBoot • C++

★ Java

★ GraphQL

 NodeJS Linux CLI

• (

# **KNOWLEDGE**

- ★ UI/UX Design
- **★** Software Architecture
- Agile methodologies
- Good coding practices
- Testing and TDD
- Search Engine Optimization
- Internationalization
- Desing Patterns

### **TOOLS**

- Git / Github
- Kanban boards
- Chrome DevTools
  iOS/Android Simulators
- Figma
- Slack
- Lighthouse
- IDEs

### **COMMUNITY**

I try to collaborate in open source and build community among IT students by attending hackathons.

# **LANGUAGES**

**English** B2 • **Spanish** native • **Catalan** native